hirewordpressexperts.com 2011-11-11

# Privacy Policy | Free Premium Wordpress Auto Install Themes Designer Plugin Development

## Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for Hire WordPress Experts

This statement applies to all products and services available at the website HireWordpressExperts.com and websites worldwide including content themes and all other services. 

* HireWordpressExperts.com collects personal information when you register for a service or use any of the freely available products on this website or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.And we may use this information for our personal and business purposes.

* HireWordpressExperts.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use HireWordpressExperts.com services in order to improve the quality of our services.  
* HireWordpressExperts.com’s servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, additionally once you use or download our products you agree to offer use the following information always, whether or not you use our products or services including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.

Uses

* We may use personal information to provide the services you’ve requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.

* We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve HireWordpressExperts.com technologies and services.  
* We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of HireWordpressExperts.com.  
* When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
* We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.  
* HireWordpressExperts.com processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.

Your choices

* You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. If you do not want to provide any information, please leave this site now.  
* We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

WEBSITE VISITORS EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE (‘THE SERVICE’) IS AT THEIR SOLE RISK. THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN ‘AS IS’ AND ‘WHEN AVAILABLE’ BASIS. HIREWORDPRESSEXPERTS.COM EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL CONDITIONS AND WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED BY LAW, CUSTOM OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY WARRANTY OF ADVERTISER ABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. HIREWORDPRESSEXPERTS.COM MAKES NO WARRANTY REGARDING ANY THEMES / GOODS / SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED FOR FREE THROUGH THE WEBSITE, OR ANY TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH THE SERVICE.
